doctoantivirus.com 2015-02-07

# DoctoAntivirus

Your privacy is important to AS Internet Ltd. To better protect your privacy, we have provided this statement, which explains our online information practices, and the choices regarding the way your personal information is collected and used. We hope this statement will increase your confidence in our Web site and enhance your experience on the Internet with AS Internet Ltd..   
Important Note: In order to receive important product updates, notification of product error fixes, or other relevant AS Internet Ltd information, you must choose to receive email messages from us. Please keep in mind that if you choose not to receive email messages, we will be unable to communicate with you via email or any other means. 

#### 1\. INFORMATION YOU PROVIDE

There are several activities on our Web site where the collection of personally identifiable information is necessary, such as when you download white papers, make a purchase, subscribe to a service or contact us. You will know when personally identifiable information is collected because you will be asked to complete a form. Generally, we collect only your name, email address on our contact us pages. When you make a purchase, our payment processor collects your credit card information. We use this information for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If payment processor has trouble processing an order, they use this information to contact you. We do not store customer credit card information in our database. We only store Name, email id and registration number mailed to them. 

#### 2\. INFORMATION WE COLLECT

If you decide to participate in our Threat community through our product Docto Antivirus then malicious files found on your PC checked by our heuristic scanner will be sent to our server for review and virus signature update. These files do not carry any private information and are either Spyware files or Virus infected files. Personally identifiable information is not tracked or recorded by AS Internet Ltd. 

#### 3\. HOW WE USE THIS INFORMATION

We may use the personally identifiable information that you provide, as well as the non-personally identifiable information that we otherwise collect about you, to fulfill your requests for our products, programs and services (e.g., billing, shipping, etc.), to respond to your inquiries about our offerings, to offer you other products, programs or services that we believe may be of interest to you, and to otherwise contact you. Our desire is to only market to our opted in users, those products, programs and services that may be of interest. You will have an opportunity to opt out or block such marketing at any time. This information is used in good faith efforts to provide you the best services and products available.   
Finally, AS Internet Ltd will not use or transfer your personally identifiable information in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you with an opportunity to opt out or block these unrelated uses. 

#### 4\. OPT IN POLICY

You will have the opportunity to opt in to receive email communications from AS Internet Ltd. You may also request at any time that AS Internet Ltd does not send any future email to you by unsubscribing from the communication. 

#### 5\. SECURITY WE PROVIDE

We have attempted to place appropriate physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and help protect against unauthorized access, maintain data security and correctly use the information we collect. Agents and contractors of AS Internet Ltd who have access to personally identifiable information are required to protect this information in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Statement and have signed NDA with the company. Although we take appropriate measures to safeguard against unauthorized disclosures of personally identifiable information, we cannot assure you that your personally identifiable information will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Statement.   
This Privacy Statement is subject to change at any time, at the discretion of AS Internet Ltd. . 

#### 6\. HOW WE HANDLE CHILDREN’S PRIVACY

We do not target or sell products, programs or services to children. Children under 13 years of age may not submit personally identifiable information without the consent of a parent. We do not provide any personally identifiable information about children less than 13 years of age to any third party for any purpose whatsoever. 

#### 7\. HOW YOU CONTACT US

If you need further assistance, if you have any questions or concerns, or if you would like to modify your personally identifiable information in any way, you may send an RFI - (request of information) using the form provided in the Contact Us section.
